prince.org 2018-06-29

# privacy policy

## What this Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers prince.org's treatment of personally identifiable information that prince.org collects when you are on the prince.org site, and when you use prince.org's services. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that prince.org does not own or control, or to people that prince.org does not employ or manage. 

## Information Collection and Use

prince.org collects personally identifiable information when you register for a prince.org account, when you use certain prince.org products or services, when you visit prince.org pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. When you register with prince.org, we ask for your name, email address, and geographic location. Once you register with prince.org and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. prince.org also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, prince.org cookie information and the page you requested. prince.org uses information for two general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services (webpages), and to contact you about promotions and site changes. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

prince.org will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. prince.org may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people in response to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or we find that your actions on our web sites violate the prince.org [User Agreement](http://www2.prince.org/user_agreement.html). 

## Cookies

prince.org may set and access prince.org cookies on your computer. The **exclusive** purpose of these cookies is to maintain 'state', such as whether or not you are logged in to your account. No personally-identifiable information, aside from possibly your login name, is stored in these cookies. prince.org's cookies and their contents are NOT available to other parties or websites. 

## Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

prince.org gives you the ability to edit your prince.org Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want prince.org to contact you about specials and new products. You may request deletion of your prince.org account by visiting our Account Deletion page, verifying your password once more and confirming your choice to terminate the account. 

## Security

Your prince.org Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas prince.org may utilize industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

prince.org may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages, and at our discretion, optionally e-mailing all users. 

## Copyright

See the terms of service for more information about copyright and other intellectual property. 

## Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions please contact us.
